（嘶嘶声）
(whooshing)
- 让我们看一下如何针对掩码语言建模
- Let's see how we can preprocess our data
预处理我们的数据。
for masked language modeling.
提醒一下，屏蔽语言建模
As a reminder, masked language modeling
主要在模型需要填补句子中的空白时使用。
is when a model needs to fill the blanks in a sentence.
为此，你只需要文本，不需要标签，
To do this, you just need texts, no labels,
因为这是一个自监督的问题。
as this is a self-supervised problem.
要将其应用于您自己的数据，
To apply this on your own data,
只要确保您在数据集的一列中
just make sure you have all your texts gathered
收集了所有的文本。
in one column of your dataset.
在开始随机掩码处理之前，
Before we start randomly masking things,
我们需要以某种方式使所有这些文本的长度相同
we will need to somehow make all those texts the same length
从而将它们一起批处理。
to batch them together.
使所有文本长度相同的第一种方法
The first way to make all the texts the same length
和我们在文本分类中所使用的相同。
is the one we used in text classification.
让我们填充短文本并截断长文本。
Let's pad the short texts and truncate the long ones.
正如我们所看到的
As we have seen
当我们处理文本分类数据时，
when we processed data for text classification,
这都是由我们的分词器完成的
this is all done by our tokenizer
并且配置相应的填充和截断选项。
with the right options for padding and truncation.
如果与我们选择的上下文长度相比，
This will however make us lose a lot of texts
我们数据集的示例很长，
if the examples in our dataset are very long,
就会使我们丢失很多文本。
compared to the context length we picked.
在这里，所有标记灰色部分都丢失了。
Here, all the portion in gray is lost.
这就是为什么第二种生成文本样本的方法
This is why a second way to generate samples of text
具有相同的长度是为了在上下文长度中
with the same length is to chunk our text
为我们的文本分块
in pieces of context lengths,
而不是在第一个数据块之后丢弃所有内容。
instead of discarding everything after the first chunk.
大概会有余数
There will probably be a remainder
长度小于上下文大小，
of length smaller than the context size,
我们可以选择保留并填充或者忽略。
which we can choose to keep and pad or ignore.
这是我们如何在实践中应用它，
Here is how we can apply this in practice,
只需在我们调用分词器时添加 return overflowing tokens
by just adding the return overflowing tokens option
选项
in our tokenizer call.
请注意这样会为我们提供更大的数据集！
Note how this gives us a bigger dataset!
如果你所有的文本很长，
This second way of chunking is ideal if all your texts
这里第二种分块方式是理想的，
are very long, but it won't work
但如果你的课文有不同的长度，那么效果就不尽人意。
as nicely if you have a variety of lengths in the texts.
在这种情况下，
In this case,
最好的选择是将所有标记的文本组合成为一个大的数据流
the best option is to concatenate all your tokenized texts
附加一个特殊的标记
in one big stream, with a special tokens
表明你何时从一份文件转到另一份文件，
to indicate when you pass from one document to the other,
然后才将该数据流分成数据块。
and only then split the big stream into chunks.
这是用代码完成的方法，
Here is how it can be done with code,
用一个循环连接所有文本
with one loop to concatenate all the texts
另一个将它分块。
and another one to chunk it.
注意在我们这里的数据集中，
Notice how it reduces the number of samples
它是如何减少样本数量的
in our dataset here,
一定有大量短条目！
there must have been quite a few short entries!
完成此操作后，掩码处理就很容易了。
Once this is done, the masking is the easy part.
在 Transformers 库中有专门为此设计的
There is a data collator designed specifically for this
数据整理器。
in the Transformers library.
你可以直接在 Trainer 中使用它，
You can use it directly in the Trainer,
或者将你的数据集转换为 tensorflow 数据集时
or when converting your datasets to tensorflow datasets
在执行 Keras.fit 之前，使用 to_tf_dataset 方法。
before doing Keras.fit, with the to_tf_dataset method.
（嘶嘶声）
(whooshing)